Neighbors 2 Sorority ising
Enjoy!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Okay.
- Okay.
Okay, so. It is well. - Okay.
Okay. - It is okay.
Do you need a pillow over his head? - Would you smother me?
What? - Is it naughty?
Just as Stella does not wake. - I keep quiet.
Okay.
Pardon. It is difficult for me. I say sounds when I love.
What was it? - Nothing.
You look like you need to throw up. - No.
Is it me? I give you nausea?
You are my teddy bear, baby. - You look bad.
I'm fine. - Have you eaten crab salad?
It's you, right? - No.
Oh no.
Okay.
It is okay. Stop.
Pardon. - Stop. But you are wildly sexy.
Thanks. - Are you okay?
Honey, I'm completely ...
Pardon. Honey, I think I'm pregnant.
Where is the fat! It's great, sweetie.
Yes ... Is it weird that I came?
4 MONTHS LATER
They are here in five minutes. - I'm fucking.
This you have done. - Well I'm nervous.
You may do later. - Shit! Okay.
Stella, you are constantly mother's dildo.
Put it away. - No.
Why does she always no? - I do not know.
Save your underwear. - Save your bongs.
Okay. What is that smell? - Bongvand.
Welcome home! - Come on in.
If therefore will buy the house. - That they might. They like it.
Great. - Pardon. We know we are annoying.
In're not annoying. What's annoying about it here?
The thing is that ...
We buy it. - It was...
It was scary. - I love the excitement.
Your daughter has been found your vibrator.
Stella ...! She finds it all the time. - Put it away, Stels.
No. - She has just learned that word.
I think it's the same, I have. - But ours is black.
Black cock.
Should not we sign? - Yes, let's do it.
SOLD
We have sold our house! - Quiet now.
I have not sold it yet. The transaction is subject.
CONDITIONAL TRADE
Are you røvrende us? - What?
I said that I knew what a conditional commerce.
Say it again, just to refresh our memory.
It is a cooling off period of 30 days, where buyers can make an overhaul.
And if all goes well, and you do not scare them away, so the deal is closed.
Do we withdraw our new house? - No.
Why not, dammit? - There was submitted several bids on it.
I would have it at any cost. - Yes it's true.
I asked three times, you realize what a cooling off period?
And again nodded in just.
Just as I do now. That was how the housing bubble occurred.
The buyers must stop by anytime. Okay?
Okay.
So do not crap the next 30 days. - Speak nicely.
She has a dildo in hand. - It's not a dildo. It is...
Toy. - From a cartoon.
A Japanese anime cartoons.
The cartoons I see every night.
We're fucking getting old. - Why do you say that?
Because our friends die. - Who dies?
Do you remember Joe Waterston? Death. - Is that right?
He was going to check a suspicious mole on her shoulder.
He was run over by a bus. Death. - Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay! I kokser that Paula is pregnant. I know how it is not.
You will be a good father. - No.
I know nothing about it. Children should not be alone.
Do not let the child stay home when going to the movies.
I knew that. - Did you?
Why do I have to? I do not understand how it can be done.
I am a good father for my one daughter. I'm being a good father of two daughters.
Stop it. - What?
You are not a good father. - Your finger to you. Yes I am.
Okay, just believe it.
Before you know it, Stella is a tween who hate you.
It is your own fault. You let her play with the dildo because you are a bad father.
We are good parents. Your shit is not to go beyond me.
Thank God I get a boy. Girls are fucking hard.
What are you talking about? - It is easier with the boys.
When a boy is sex, it's fat. When a girl gets sex, it's bad.
No. - Do your daughter well have sex?
"Hey, Jimmy. Stella is just was fucked. Come and drink some beers.
WELCOME, NEW STUDENTS!
WOULD YOU HAVE FRIENDS?
SISTERS FOR LIFE?
SEARCH PHI LAMBDA!
Welcome to Phi Lambda.
It is an exciting year. If you are lucky -
- And gets busy, you become a member of a sisterhood and make friends for life.
We have installed a hot tub.
We have brand new feather duvets.
We have a new chef, and all food is gluten-free.
Hello. What are you doing?
I would clearly have offered you the first. Pardon.
Pecking order. You must have the first boom.
No, we do not smoke joints. Never. Turn it off.
Glass.
Glass. - It cost $ 12.
There is hash oil in it. - Glass.
Your party must suck the meanest ass if you do not have to smoke pot.
The girls' student associations should not hold celebrations.
Seriously? - Girls Association Doctors must not keep partying.
It's only boys who can hold celebrations. Check it.
What? Fester not you?
Of course, you dolt. We just do it with the boys.
Hello. - Hi.
I'm sorry if I interrupted you. - I do not know anyone.
I read just some old text messages.
I did too. I had not got any.
Looking Phi Lambda? - Yes, I'm Beth.
Shelby. - It is exciting. First boy celebration.
Yes of course. Clear...
Drop a tier in the bucket.
Hello. A tier in the bucket. - Okay.
You're okay. Just go.
No. - That's all I have.
No. Uninvited guest! - Thank you!
NO MEANS YES
Damn, slut.
The room is the one big arrow pointing upstairs where they can fuck us.
Holy shit.
So what? Do you upstairs?
Who you ask? - It does not really matter.
No. - Allows you?
It was not what I had expected. - Bummer.
They play the same song over and over again. - Yes. It is piss annoying.
Hi, I'm Nora. - Yes ...
We progresses. - Yes.
How cool, I found you. Taber Fest. I thought they were funny.
Yes. I did not feel safe. - There was a rape mood.
To be honest, I have never taken drugs before.
But college is about new experiences, and now I'm here.
And now I smoke pot.
Not too much.
Okay, it's a great lung.
Are you okay? - Do you want some water?
I think she should Orle.
If she ørler, I do it too.
You are beautiful. - She's fine.
This is just me.
Smoke never in school? - What were you doing?
Have I not told? I have been in a steady relationship since third grade.
Just like Cory and Topanga?
Stop! - Yes exactly.
That is so sweet. - Yes, exactly.
I've loved with three men. Two of them were black.
And one was inside.
I've tried it all, but ...
But what? - Everything except just the one thing.
Have you never licked ass on a guy?
No no. I think...
Highschool was bummer. Now that we are honest.
My father wanted me home early.
He gave me a rape whistle and talk about behavior on the way here.
Therefore I had not the wild social life, when I was in highschool.
You do not need to say it. We are completely with.
Did you have any friends?
Knock, knock! I'll just.
What about girls? - Hey, Dustin.
It smells a little weird.
Are you done? First warning.
It's just bullshit!
You're adults. I go to college. - You made me piss scared.
Have all of you smoked? - Yes.
Hell! I knew it fucking!
Do not take drugs.
Well? Is that understood?
See you later, tosser. Grab me if you need me.
Frankly. - Holy shit.
I am so tired of guys who will decide for us.
We're not little girls. We are strong, adult women.
The girls can not even hold parties. - And we can not enjoy ourselves here.
You know what we do?
We make our own fraternity, having parties that we like.
And then we sisters for life. - Yes.
I'll be your sister. - I do too.
BFF!
Did not I say that you should shut your ass?
Pokeraften!
Selfiestang.
I have designed Outback Steakhouses. Many of them.
However, your app will change the world. - A cock at a time.
"En pik ad gangen."
It's a bold idea. A photo app that makes one's dick bigger.
Your TED talk was good. - Thank you so on.
I have just successfully. - I'm still armor.
It is not the worst, but there are many rules.
I do not know why I have to go with the camera. I will not shoot myself.
Can not beat them, stop himself to them.
What about you?
Work wise it has been bummer.
They do not use models with no shirt on anymore. So now I walk around in here.
It looks as mellow out. - And you know what?
I am six years older than the next oldest.
I had to take a guard for my boss because he was going to prom.
Why is everyone in retail so young?
I feel really underrated.
And ... klart.
But I at least you. I love you.
Delta Psi. - Once a week. Every Monday.
Exactly. - Well, Darren. What puts you?
I put ... it all.
A good hand. What do you have? Full house? - Hopefully one day.
Holy shit. Our song. What happens?
Oh God.
The Greeks said that all of it is half of a whole.
Peter, you're the half that makes me whole.
Oh god, it happens really?
I do not know the rules about who should be free.
You go anyway not ring.
But wear it for my sake.
Will you marry me? - Yes, why not! Give it on.
1, 2, 3!
USA!
Has he told you about college? It was wild.
He was too ill. He tufted all the girls.
No. - You were a little crazy.
I would just figure it out. - While wading in pussy.
It was not ... - I licked all too pussy.
Not as much as him.
That's okay, we just talk about our commune?
Darren could just move into. He is here almost every night.
Thank you.
Seriously, it's okay that Darren will move into -
- And you stop to stay here?
What do you mean? Why? - We're engaged.
What had you imagined?
That you would stay in your room and that I would stay at mine. To our dying day.
Darren're working from home -
- So we had intended to turn it into an office.
And maybe one day ...
... A children's room.
Babies are small. - Yes.
They are the size of a small shoe box.
They do not take up a whole room. - I try to find a counterargument.
It was damn fun. I just took the piss out of you.
I must get out for a run. - Now?
I love you damn. Come here.
Love you. - You too.
Teddy, do not just wear shoes?
The owner of the house is super cool. He's like me.
He is sweaty. I can do everything I want.
Keeping parties, stay up all night -
- Play with your phones and snap chat all the shit.
Smoking pot. But did you afford it? What's your name?
Shelby. - I'm Team Shelby.
And you? - Nora.
I am Team Nora. What? - Beth.
Yes it is good.
Usually it costs 25,000 a month, but I can get it for the 5000th
Can I put 5 kg? - No.
My phone rings. Moment.
Called the?
I'll get it right. These are some others who want to start a girl Association.
They are very alternative. What should I do?
What do we do? - We can not afford.
What do we do? - Do not look at me.
There sits a beautiful centaur and thinking.
Who are you? - I'm Teddy Sanders.
I have lived here.
Why hobble you? - I ran here without shoes on.
Very far.
Are you considering renting the house? - Maybe.
What do you mean by that? - We will start an association.
Without the system. Where you can do as you like and keep the wildest celebrations.
En pigeforening, der holder fester?
- Kappa Nu.
What's wrong with the boy celebrations? - Everything.
We stayed in some great parties here. Beggars and flax.
Directors and koncernhoer. Fresh guys and provinshoer.
They are super sexist. The theme is always ho.
I mean ... Oh god.
Oh no. Oh God.
I see what you mean. - It does not matter right now.
We have to find something else. We can not afford housing.
How much money do you have?
Perhaps a few thousand, if we throw everything. But it is for the whole year.
Use them on payment and hold one shooting day.
I get membership fees and an army that earns money for you.
And then you get your union.
Have you had a rental agreement?
I did not understand some of what you said.
Last week I slept in a bunk bed.
Yes, and I can not boil an egg.
We are 18. We know what we want but not how to achieve it.
I drove Delta Psi in four years. I can help you.
Okay.
I mean ... Can I use it for anything?
Yes, we can really use for anything.
Believe In It?
It should be celebrated. - Yes!
Okay! - Shall we take a ride on the cable car?
Tear it up. - Now I just watch.
We would do two at a time. Try to see. Delta Psi!
Did anything happen? - I'm fine.
The booklets I am not.
We'll take it.
Sweaty.
He you okay? - Yes.
I am up and running. The house is perfect for us.
It becomes fat.
See you. - Thank you.
Is it Teddy Sanders?
Pis. - Who is it?
Drive. I'll explain later.
Mac, Kelly. Hello. So what? - So what?
What are you doing here? I live here. - Yes. Who was it?
You must not think of. - Okay.
Well, I see you move. - We're moving up.
It could have done when I lived here.
It would be grease. - That we were not ready.
I am punished because of you two.
Beware! - It's hard to get work.
Hard. - Yes.
What are you doing here? - It will find out soon enough.
What does that mean? - It should not think about.
It was good to see the lines. I've missed jer. See you soon.
Okay, hi.
It was as weird.
Do you want to be included in the coolest
girl association? So it is here.
Welcome to Kappa Nu!
Welcome, new students!
Vi er Kappa Nu!
Do you have friends for life?
Substances!
Join!
Hot guy!
What the hell...
People. - Are there some who move into?
Can we just get past, girls? Hello. - Hi.
What the hell ... - What's happening here?
"Så er det nu, Kappa Nu."
Hi! We are your neighbors. Mac and Kelly.
I Kelly. - Are your parents here?
No. Meet girls from Kappa Nu. - What is it?
That's our girl unification.
Hello, neighbors!
You want a beer or a mocktail? A mother-mocktail? Congratulations.
I would like to have a mocktail. - Insert the woman a mocktail.
Thanks. - Thank you.
What the hell ...! - What do we do?
I have no idea! Buyers will damn not live next to a girl Association.
Is it now, I'll freak out? - No.
Should I cry? - No.
We must get them to take it easy. - They just behave.
No parties during the withdrawal period.
Afterwards, they just go crazy.
Hello. So what?
Can we just take a quick word?
We will ask you something.
We just sold our house with a 30-day cooling-off period.
If something happens that scares buyers away -
- We are faced with two houses and is on the ass.
So it would be cool if I took it quietly -
- And did not hold celebrations for 30 days.
So we are away. Then you can go crazy.
A very large part of the reason -
- We made the association, was -
- The boy associations may well hold celebrations, but the girl's associations can not do.
Is that right? - Why does festivities lot to us.
I would probably like to see your daughter have the same rights as the guys.
I like man only agree with you.
I can only support your cause.
But my wife has made a few thoughts on -
- How you can approach it in a different way. Kelly?
Drive.
We may well find a compromise, right?
I ... - There I was told no! What, then, neighbors?
Teddy? - Welcome to "soon".
What do you mean? - I said: It will find out soon enough.
It took place shown only in your head.
I am mentor for the association.
Can you be? - Yes.
Why are you doing it? - Why flying butterflies?
In order to gather nectar. - Well, I only know what I do.
And I ensure that there can be partied in the house.
What? - So let's makse it out!
I've missed jer.
The rules for successful girl unification. Rule no. 1:
Use the money forehead to keep track of the cash.
5 cans per month is enough for rent.
Rule no. 2: Embrace new applicants. You can dress them like idiots.
Minion. - They have a whole army of Minions fun.
I love Minions and now they force me to hate them.
Rule no. 3: Hold celebrations that shows who you are.
Hillary Clinton, Jeanne d'Arc commands you to send jointen on.
First Lady Clinton? - Or Senator Clinton?
Or future President Clinton?
Oprah, we need beer. - Look under your chairs.
There is beer for everyone!
Beer to you, beer for you, beer for you!
I love you, Oprah.
Are sweet dampen you? - Shut up!
MOVIE NIGHT
"A tear in the sky"
I am so grateful.
I just love you so much.
It's unfair. You're too young.
SHELBY lose your virginity-FEST
Please just shut up! - Stop now!
Come on, everyone! We want pussy!
We want pussy!
Come on. - We beg!
I can not let a girl association that tries to be independent.
It's a PR nightmare. - Why?
For example: "Sexist female dean closes girl unification."
It is inversely sexism. And it is in itself sexist.
Conversely sexism does not exist, white man.
How should you not speak to me. I am jew. I belong to a minority.
There are fewer of you, like with labradoodler.
After three warnings must be closed. - You can get tons of warnings.
I can see that we do not follow the rules.
Plan B.
We hope this translates in that you change your mind.
Do we have a deal, rector? - No.
The finger to you! - Give the gas tax.
Do you speak such in front of your daughter? - We're good parents.
She can not remember shit. - Jo.
Nej. Se her. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck.
Ser hun "Goodfellas"?
It is you who are fools. I do not know what she sees.
What should we do? The house must be reviewed.
The buyers can come and say:
"There are a few leaks, and so live there 20 psychopathic teenagers next door."
We have two houses. - As we lose.
And then we're screwed. - We are totally screwed. Hey darling.
We must of them. - I could not talk to the girls.
The boys we could talk to. They looked at us as if we were their grandparents.
Yes. How to become Stella not.
She will always be our best friend. - We're a team.
Not too, Stella? Come over here. - Come.
Do you want to come here? - What the hell's wrong with her?
Play with your toys, baby. - Play with your toys. Give it a kiss.
Who listens to young people? Their parents. - The known. Their parents.
So what?! Hi Dad.
You should stay on a college and not in a dilapidated villa.
If you want to stay as a vagabond murderer?
I can do what I want here. That's the whole point of college.
When are you starting to speak like Eminem?
Here's how I talk. It's ridiculous.
How old is the pizza?
East he muggen. - East he mug.
I eat it whenever I want. - Have you inherited mit dummegen?
Have you learned to be as dumb as boys?
Back to college. - No! I've chosen to live like this.
I would only stay in Kappa Nu.
My little girl is growing up.
Thank you Father.
Should I invite you and your friends at brunch?
I need a pair of jeans. - Then we go out and shop.
How did it go? - Are they all right now? Punished them?
I did my best, but it did not. - What do you mean?
You can get them all, when they are two.
Yes. - It's getting harder.
I do not understand a word of what she says.
But it was good to see her. It's so quiet at home without her.
I manage it.
What a beautiful girl.
Can I hold her? - No, no, no. You do not have to.
Is that a dildo dressed as a princess? - No.
It is an af vor time popular cartoon characters.
Thank you for trying.
Called in to my parents?
Yes, we did. - Yes, we did actually.
Did I? - It is about 30 days.
In 30 days, the withdrawal period is over! - More we do not ask.
Then there is the war. - No. Why should there be war?
There is a war. - We started it and we calls off it.
There is a war.
Hey, Mac! - Hey, Big Mac!
Although! There has moved more into.
In staying you illegally on private property.
Beth must have some sunscreen on. - She performs shown.
Where are you going? - Leave me alone.
Where am I?!
Oh no. I have killed a girl.
I'm on painkillers, your bastard! Kappa Nu!
What the hell's wrong with you ?!
Get out, you beast!
It does not work! You just makes them more sexy!
I do not like it!
What was it? - A bird?
What the hell is that?
No! - Tampons! Where is it gross.
Hold så op, I Udyr!
Hold op!
- Mac!
The second window is open!
It was really fun. Where did the theater blood from?
From our scabbards. - Was it real?
It was shot out of our wombs.
Have just thrown ...
It's crazy obnoxious.
Why did you do it? There you went too far.
You are supersexistisk. It was skidesjovt.
You had thought it would be fun if it had been a bag of dicks.
No...
A bag of dicks.
Okay, that got me. It is fun.
First review is tomorrow.
We need help. - We need to get the girls away.
Between the hours of ten and five. - If buyers see the girls, it's over.
The girls are far-fetched. They are from another planet.
Yes, they are worse than the guys. - Brainstorming.
A variant of a classic:
Flax before guys. - No.
It will not work. We always flax first.
It worked with the boys. - Girls are much smarter than guys.
It is sexism! - No, not when it's on fire.
I do not know what sexism is. - Men's rights.
Fuck you. - Why claws in you?
Do you have touched poison ivy? - No. We've got bed bugs.
Add! No!
Need to make me embarrassed? - Do not embarrass us!
We have mastered it. We disinfect the house and stay away for three days.
The clothes are full of bedbugs. - Quiet! They will be infected in a hurry.
Here are some new members.
Those are my favorite jeans. - I shit on. In with them.
I can not see shit. - There are many lice in the sheets.
I can feel them! Get it off!
Good morning! Now we come in. Take clothes.
Hi! Welcome. It's good to see you.
Welcome back.
I have taken my guy.
No, he must see if here is fungus. - Do you think this is fungus?
Here smelled weird lately. - We just want to be on the safe side.
Cloudy. That's why we're here. - What's happening over there? New tenants?
Yes, the new family is starting to disinfect. A nice, quiet family.
There must be a large family.
Yes. - It is a very religious family.
They are Jews and very sweet.
Why did you do that? - Well, they are cute.
I actually think they get there. See! It is our Jewish neighbors.
Proof that they exist.
She is pregnant. - She has a small jew in the oven.
Let's see if there are sponge. - Come into your home.
We begin in your kitchen.
Here's weird. - Yes.
Where do you live, Teddy?
I help some girls to make an association.
They live in our house. I'm moving in enough. It is a great achievement for me.
Okay ... It's super weird. - No, it's super normal.
If it makes you happy ... - You stay out!
Relax, Teddy.
Now I've finally found something I'm good at and then criticize me?
I just think that it is a little odd -
- That an adult man is to found a girl Association.
Girls have no right to throw a party. - It is not a right.
Yes it is. Bak me up, Garf. - Keep me out.
I am your best friend. I'm just trying to be honest.
It was you a long time. - What?
You did not tell me your secret, while we were in college.
What's happening to you?
You said it to Garf first! - Yes, he experimented with guys.
Sometimes you have to suck dick to discover that you do not like dick.
You're just angry because you're lost. The rest of us have moved on.
Garf's armor, Scoonie has his own company, I'm getting married.
And you move into the girl unification of hell.
The sisters are better brothers to me than you. You're not my brother.
Do not say anything you can not take in you again. Guys before flax.
Do not call them flax. It's not working anymore.
We need to talk about our economy. It does not look good.
Fumigation was animals. We have only two buckets back. What should we do?
Our Minions can make money for us. - They have enough to do.
Maranda, sell your brother not pot?
Yes, it was what I said. My brother, Daffodil.
Why do not we buy pot for all our money and sell it for outdoor party?
Yes, dammit! - We can score box.
Good idea. We write Kappa Nu with glitter on our T-shirts.
Bad idea. You can not serve enough of it.
What? - All sell pot to the party.
We sit on potmarkedet by gossiping about all the other drug dealers in the city.
And then Kappa Now the only group that sells pot to the party.
Hell, yes! - It's fucking brilliant!
Look here. It is very risky.
We sell ... - Pot!
We smoke ... - Pot!
What do we sell? - Pot!
Hell!
You behave like children. Now I listen.
I've tried it. I know what I'm doing.
I have no knowledge ...
What happens to Teddy? He seems angry.
Has he got quarter life crisis? It is what it is.
We drop him. It is a shame.
Yes, but it's for his own good. But he's so delicious.
Yes, but it's for his own good. How about others?
It sucks, but yes. You're right.
Am I right? - We voted on it. You must leave.
When? - Right now. With our phones.
What? No. It can not do this to me.
I thought we were sisters. Should not we be a team?
Why do you do it? It can not do this to me.
I have quit my job. - That we asked you to leave early.
I have raised my annuity. - What is it?
I do not know ... now. - I'm glad your help.
We have folded their wings and fly like women.
I have only you. Are we in this together?
You are not like us, man. You are old.
You are right. I've played on the wrong team.
See you.
Okay...
I was not too hard on him, right?
No, no, you did well.
It was good.
Now that dad is not here anymore, are we on a rampage.
Is the emergency services? I want to report three places -
- Which sells marijuana. Yes, ganja.
Down on the floor! - Down!
Take it in your mouth! Yes, do you like!
What are you doing, Watkins? - Today you are with to learn.
Ned!
What the hell ...! - You do not go to police school anymore!
Ned ... Sorry. I'll have to go to the station.
We have bottled water in the car. We can buy some food on the way.
Think that we made it through. - Thank God.
Yes, dammit! - It's over, if they see the girls.
I rush totally over it.
I need to chill with a joint, but my drug dealer has nothing.
Good luck finding anything. - Hell!
How did you get in? - It does not matter.
I will help you to stop the girl unification.
Yes, I change side.
Sweet! - Yes!
I am also still fresh, Kelly. - Oh hold up.
It hurts me, although I should not fuck.
He just kidding. - Kappa Nu set at potmarkedet.
Oh no! - Oh yeah.
No other vendor pot before Monday. - Will they sell to me?
Nej. De har tre kilo pot.
They can sell it for $ 50 program if they want to.
That's $ 16,000 half a kilo. If they sell it all, they get 112,000.
It shall we do. - You are good at math.
No, but I'm good pot. - It's the same.
No, this is pot. - Just play, it's meat. Try.
Why should I buy meat? - Because you're hungry.
Do you think burgers? - Steaks.
How much does a gram steaks? Why should I sell steaks in grams?
Fine. - They will sell it for outdoor party.
They get enough cooling-off period.
What should we do? - Stealing it. So they do not have to rent.
Their members go to other associations and then it's over.
What do you get out? - I would honestly just appreciated.
How the hell do we beat them? They are 15th
No. They are 15 individuals. They have no unity.
They forget the most important rule: There is no aces in the "community".
Yes, there are two. - There is actually only one.
No. - Yes, in the middle.
It is an L. - The two s's are around.
F-æ-l-s-e-s-l-e-s-k-a-b.
What? - I forget the P.
F-æ-l-l-e-s-k-a-p-a-t...
Fælleskapat? - Yes.
Is teat so dumb? - Now we have come out on the wrong track.
We need to find out how we can infiltrate the outdoor party.
Outdoor Fest? - Outdoor Fest.
Outdoor Fest. - Outdoor Fest.
Potkage!
Pot for women. Only 20 dollars.
Kappa Nu-pot. It is charity spot. - Potkage. Only 20 dollars a piece.
You are fucking scary to look at. - People love clowns.
Hell! - Do not do that!
You do not again. So I just give birth.
Here's the plan. I go up on stage and dance.
I'll distract the girls, while Mac runs to steal the pot.
Kelly and Paula, are driving getaway cars.
I am pregnant and can not run around here.
I do not think all the girls get distracted when you're dancing.
They do usually. - I do not even know where we are.
Okay. I'm ready.
Shit! Hell! No!
I have no baby oil.
It is crucial. Baby Oil provide two more lines.
Vent.
Just come. Of where it warm. It is really hot.
It burns! Rub it in.
Holy shit. - Oh God.
Kelly, what the hell are you doing? - We are busy.
Take your thighs. - Okay.
What's up! Clear stage.
I have nothing to say. This song is for my girlfriends in Kappa Nu.
We have had some problems in the past, but I love you.
DJ, then shake ass.
You run the store, right? - Jo.
Okay...
Oh no!
He showed dick!
Oh no. - The pot!
It is gone! Oh no!
The damn monkey has taken our pot! - Get hold of it!
Get the pot!
I hate clowns!
Shit! - Find another way out.
I'll get another car. Move! - Oh no!
Away!
Shit! - Move!
I have your pot!
Where is my pot? Come on!
He who laughs last! - Stop!
It's a waste! It is not pot! - The pot!
The clown fooled us!
Shit!
Wait. Mac, you can comfortably.
Pis!
Right! - I athletics champion, your slut!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Holy shit! - Now she comes!
Free can! - Her!
Free can!
Pot to the people!
How will we pay the rent?
Your muscles turns me on.
I pump a kilo! - Do you have pain?
They are a little heavy. - Yes.
I love you! Hell...
And.
It is a shame, but it's also pretty funny.
Thanks, man. - The girls were wild.
No, the girls were too wild until we got track of them.
I got control of them. - You can get a handle on all situations.
For parents are wise, and children are røvdumme.
I've figured it out. - You need to know the answer to this:
Who is Teddy Sanders? Important questions.
Before I achieved something, I asked myself: "Who is Mac Radner?
"Who are you, Kelly Dhundee?" - Is your maiden name Dundee?
No, Dhundee. There is an H. - Just like Crocodile Dundee?
No, it's a different name.
Yes, but it's a bit of a coincidence.
Crocodile Dundee.
- Nej!
No no. - You need to find out who you are.
What are you doing today? - Yes, what is your plan of life?
I will play on my phone and walk around until I get tired.
And then I lie down to sleep in my car. I think.
It is sad. Do you want to sleep here?
Do you have space? - You can sleep on Stella's room.
She takes up so much.
And.
Thanks. - No, we say thank you.
It means a lot to me. - Yes, but it's nothing.
Yes, it is.
So.
Thanks. Do you have more of these?
Yes, there are plenty in the kitchen. Just go. - Is the baby food?
Yes, so ... - Babies get good food.
De er faith. - Bare tag.
That is so sweet. Watch him.
He inhaled so much potrøg that he had fallen over.
Okay.
We have lost all our pot, and we have to pay rent. What should we do?
I thought you stopped the old. - It's not my fault.
I is a human female. I had to see it.
I stood for whipped cream ... - We were together about it.
She stood for pot. You...
Stop it! Can not you see what happens?
That's what the old ones. They want to divide us along.
They know that we can not lose if we stand together.
For we are sisters!
Finally I belong somewhere.
I did not know that college could be so fat.
I've never had so much fun, and I've been at Space Camp.
I have not slept for a week. I will not miss anything. You are so cool.
We will always be sisters. What do you call a house united women?
And fuck? - Nej, in pigestudenterforening.
Okay. Here's the problem.
We can not solve our problems because we are at war.
What should we do? - They must taste their own medicine.
They would drive a wedge between us.
So what do we do?
We create a rift between them. Or is this game?
No one would say that it was the game, if you were a man.
Exactly. Give the gas queen.
So we do it!
What do you think about it?
Come and get me, my prince.
Come and get me. No.
Yellow stars. What color should her dress have?
What happens to the water? - It boils.
Great, right? And now the eggs in.
Coming eggs in the water? - Yes. Now you just watch.
Did you hear that?
It is hot! - I told you so!
I thought it was the jacuzzi-hot. - No, it's boiling hot.
Now comes the eggs in. They must be hard boiled.
Do not. The melt. - No, they are just hard.
Why should they be hard? - What do you mean?
Pasta softens it. - You've got something.
She looks fantastic. Try to see.
It is a beautiful color.
I love to color.
She is dressed very much out.
She stands in a garden somewhere. In a dress.
You see sometimes people I do not see?
Just say it.
Honey, I'm home!
I've always wanted to say. - It is fun. I say it constantly.
Dear Mac. It is not good for us.
I'm out of it. From Kelly.
What? - What's she doing? It's a joke.
She takes the piss out of me. - It's bullshit.
LOL! You got me. You are funny.
I totally freaked out about some things. Do not call.
It's far out! - It's moving.
I'll call her. - Clear.
Pis. He is calling. - Reject the call.
What happens?
It is okay. - Hang up.
Just take it easy. It is not a problem.
What things? - Cases.
What matters? - You know that.
No. - Yes you do. Stuff.
Can not we just talk? Where are you?
Where's she gone? - I know.
What?
I've been up all night. I am very uneasy.
Send me a text message. I am uneasy.
I am beside myself about some things. Do not call.
What? Are you with Jimmy?
No. And he does not say where I am.
Jimmy...!
Come on. I'm hungry! - I tweet. Spell straight to Trump.
Jimmy. - Hey, I need.
Where is he? - Who?
You are bad at lying! Where is he? - I do not know.
He said you'd say. Say it then.
Hello, Kell. - Mac is gone. Jimmy knows where he is.
However, where he is, dammit! - I do not know.
Now you can protect him! Tell me where he is!
No. He is happier for you than I am.
You are lying! Where the hell is he? - I'm not lying.
Why do I so ugly? - My husband is gone.
And this man knows where he is. - Say it, dammit.
It was completely unnecessary.
Say it. Otherwise, she says you. - He is in prison for child pornography.
What? - No. I do not know.
No, no, no! - Call him!
Okay! Here! Hell.
I got an ulcer.
Why do you Jimmys phone?
Are you here? Are you hiding?
I am at your office. I've been looking for you.
I have gone to meet you.
- Where?
In Sydney in Australia. Outside the opera house.
Are you in Australia? - Yes, the trip took 18 hours. What happens?
We have been hacked! - "Kappa Nu tricked you."
Kappa Nu! Drillekrig! Airbags!
- Airbags!
This is not a drill!
Let the ass!
I'll take the trip over the bridge, and then I'll come home.
The fridge is almost new.
Cheap pensioner shit Buy something for your grandmother!
Pensionistlort?
"Kappa Nu steals from you."
Do they have stolen from us? - Shit!
We must call the police. - We can not!
We stole their pot! Girls are worse than the guys.
I know that it is not feminist, but fuck it!
They took fortunately not Stellas toys. - Stop! I have not slept for four days!
It is three o'clock at night where I am in Australia.
We are totally screwed.
We are in the drug war with some teenagers. We go bankrupt.
We have made so many bad choices. - Soon we have two girls.
We can not even take care of one. - I am a bad parent.
No, I am. - No.
Stop. - It's me who's bad.
No, it's me. Last week I found her with a potkugle in the mouth.
Indica or Sativa? - Indica. She slept nine hours in a row.
But I lost her on the head when she was six months.
I did too. - What?
I went to Taco Bell and forgot her. She was near death due to a gordita!
I am a bad parent. - It's both of us.
Oh no, it's Broker-Wendy.
My clients prefer the offer back. - What?
We drove by and saw Kappa Nu. - Where'd you get the name from?
I have also gone to college. Omega Theta. "Full speed!"
Why is he here? You are my clients.
Because you forgot to say that there is a fraternity next door.
Congratulations. I have hired a fool. - Close the ass.
Close ass. - Close the ass.
Close self ass. - We fucked once.
It's irrelevant. - We regret the contrary, not with each other.
Can we not try to undo together? - It's some lovely girls.
Super Cute girls. - Hardly. We saw them rob your home.
Thank stopped them! - Stood In just and so on?
It was not how it was. - I did not mention the student union.
Can not we work something out?
Yes, I can conjure away the union before tomorrow.
POSTPONEMENT
Is it true? - No, it's just the old.
No, the landlord said it yourself. - Maybe it was just the old.
No, we have been evicted. We do not rent.
We spent our money on pot.
We need five buckets of money. Otherwise we will be evicted tomorrow.
We lose the house. - We lose our sisters.
And we have no friends like in high school.
How do the boys money? - They take admission to festivities.
People will not pay an entrance fee here. - The boys do not come and say:
"You look good in your everyday clothes." - Wait.
"Nice sweater." - I have an idea!
Okay. - But I will not break you about it.
We hold a party. - We lose money when we're having a party.
Not one of the great parties where we have fun.
We keep a shit boy celebration.
The boys must be so loved it that they will pay an entrance fee -
- And tell their rotten friends about it so they will also pay an entrance fee.
Just like the night we met. - Otherwise we lose the house.
And so we lose Kappa Nu. I will not lose jer.
Okay. - We'll tell the girls.
We will not lose the association and housing.
So we have to dress a little "rougher" than we usually do.
I am naughty. I tufted pizza tender and gave him five stars on Yelp.
You have chips in their hair. - Yes.
INVITES YOU !!!
FOR PARTY
ENTRY: $ 20
BOYS ARE WELCOME!
The video looks just like a million. - We're screwed! We go bankrupt.
No, look good on it.
It is stung by them. They have everything they hated.
Holy shit. - They are vulnerable.
The party will finance the house.
He is right. - If we close it closes the association.
Now, the adult ones lost. - I'll give them all lost.
We do what adults do best: To prevent young people from having fun!
Come on in!
I hope you close yourself into a little later.
You are funny.
Call your friends and tell them to come.
We must close the shit at any cost. I go in and close it from the inside.
Me and Kelly calling the cops and closes the outside.
From the inside, from the outside. Understood.
Now I am ready. - Yes. Now I am ready.
Honestly, man!
Hello. - What then, Kappa Nu?
It only costs 20 Come here. They are drenched. Seriously.
There is ridiculously many delicious bitches. There are delicious bitches everywhere.
They are ready to be popped.
How much money forehead do we have?
Punch tastes weird. - We have not made punch.
I commence phase second
Phase 2 is to hold the old from calling the cops.
If you see some old people, stop them.
I do not like it here. - No.
You should not drink it. - My tongue is numb.
Among the lines with people. - Yes, from, from, from.
Excuse me.
Good party. I write to my friends. - No. They do not think you're funny.
Oh damn! - Are you okay? What's wrong?
I should not have eaten the McRib. It is nothing. I just cramp.
I think it is labor. - No, she has first forward tomorrow.
It is clearly labor. Take time on them. - It is over. I'm fine.
She did not labor. Then she slipped.
Go after her. - She decide over his body.
Last night of freedom! - I love you!
We must be up to the relay. What are you doing? You should not drink it there.
What is it? - You never drink the punch! Come on.
I saw you with Teddy. Why were you with Teddy?
We interrupt the flow and closes the party.
What? - I was totally stiff quickly.
I did too. And I've only been drinking punch.
There is provided a Cosby on us!
And!
Kappa Nu, then it's goodnight.
They must have another power source.
Banana!
I have to stop you!
Look at how big my tongue. - Look how big my tongue.
Okay, now we will call to panserne. - Hello!
It will be difficult without a phone, right? - Come with it!
No! - Put it!
What the hell? - It's called a wire, you fool.
Lede pensioner phone!
Where are our phones? - These?
How did you get them?
Come on!
I could not find the relay. - Do you have a phone?
No, I have run out of data. - Shit!
I'm in here.
Do not try to find me.
Even close.
It's getting warmer.
It's getting warmer. Bingo!
Shit. - No!
I shut you not out until we have enough money. There are energy bars in the corner.
There is water. And it says a fucking bucket. - Shit!
Come back. - Kelly!
Shelby! Come back! - Help us!
Now you come back.
She has locked it.
Okay, calm on. Use your head.
Okay, now you need to hear. We throw everything we can at the door.
What are you doing? - I shit when I'm nervous.
Look away. - Suck it up again. We're going out.
Of the road. - Strong man.
Pis! Okay.
Shit! Pardon.
Pardon. We try something else. - I am alright.
Shit. Are you okay, Mac? - Yes.
You destroyed my bike. - It did not work.
No. Can you do it again? - I think...
There we have it. How do we get out.
It's too high. - No.
I have not the key. Quick Connect, we'll run through the wall.
I can not, but I know a lot about airbags.
Quietly.
Okay.
If we do it right -
- Shoot airbag us up through the ventilation shaft.
Okay. Who does that?
I do. - Thank God. I do not think I can.
Are you okay? - Are we still friends after this?
Want to be seen? - Yes.
When the war is over, that means I still matter to you?
And.
Prove it. - Prove what?
Give me a hug.
It is not necessary. - Give me a hug.
Give me a real hug. - Why?
It strengthens the bond.
Come on.
I appreciate you, man. Thanks.
It's actually nice.
No, it's so nice.
Yes like that. - It's strong.
Yes. - Okay, now it becomes too much.
Thank you my friend. - I like it vennepis.
We are friends. - Yes. So we do it.
Before you do, we may just be absolutely sure -
- That you stand right under it.
Clear. - 1, 2, 3!
Oh no! Are you okay?
Yes Yes. I have mastered it.
No. You've certainly got concussion.
I just need to have 10 minutes. - No. Now I will take over.
Careful.
Okay. This is it.
Now I will deliver the family.
Are you okay? - It worked!
I have purchased the old road.
They are locked up in the garage. - What is it?
It's a shit party. - I will not be here anymore.
It runs for us. - Do it?
Wet T-shirt contest!
You are all winners! - Do not!
I stop.
So do I. - I am out of here.
No, you must not. We will figure it out. Wait!
Wait. Now, let's just talk about it.
Stop a second. Wait.
Become now just below. Try to hear.
The party has been even greater.
What happened? - I've got Rohypnol.
So if I want to have sex with me, so it is now.
The plan is almost complete. The old is gone. We Kappa Nu.
It was not what we wanted with Kappa Nu.
Stops In only? - You have ruined it.
I look like Nicki Minaj! - I look like Snooki!
I am the only one who tried to save it, and then progresses I just.
It falls apart. - Should we destroy their friendship?
We are in the middle of the withdrawal period.
We tried. We worked hard for it. It does not.
We have the whole system against us. Longer is not.
Okay. I give up.
The world is sexist, and we can not change.
Think that it's over. - Now I lose all my friends.
I wish we had never created the association.
It is not good. - No.
They're just young.
Hello! Women!
Take care, however, together, dammit.
You are strong women. In trying to challenge the system.
I just moved from home, and I'm scared.
Yes, I'm afraid. - I know what it's about.
Yes we do. What is it about?
I must not fail yourselves. - Say something more.
When you're going down, to travel themselves. They can not keep you down.
Did you straight on that? - Yes.
Kelly.
Say that they have to make out with each other.
It is those Kappa Nu, not the house.
It is you who are Kappa Nu, not the house.
The mother is right. What are we doing?
We hold a party, we like, and stores the worries for tomorrow.
Never mind if we lose it there. I hope we do not lose it here.
Girls ... - I'm so happy.
Boy, I'd like to see them kissing.
Good speech, sweet. Where did you get it?
We have a daughter, baby. - What about the cooling-off period?
I do not know, but it should be done. - Okay.
Jimmy! Where are you?
Shit! Paula.
I think I was wrong. It is not McRib'en.
Oh god, no!
It has its feet after me. It has broken through.
Run in the hospital!
I love you. - I love you too.
We lose our house? - We have no money, then yes.
So it must have gas!
It's a great party! It succeeded you. A girl association may hold celebrations.
We would like to be members. - Who are we?
Throw the membership fee in the bucket, if you will enrolled.
Do we go with the hoodie? I like nice clothes.
No, I can go into it, I will.
Welcome to Kappa Nu! - Welcome!
Come on in! Money in the bucket.
Yes, money in the bucket.
Pete. Wake up, Pete.
What the hell? What happens ... What are you doing?
Take it easy. Try to hear. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I did not do well when you were engaged.
I thought I lost you. But then I realized that I never lose you.
For we will always be brothers, right?
Always.
I do not lose my best friend. I get my best friend's husband.
For satan!
It is okay. Teddy and I have just become friends again.
May I ask you something? - Yes.
Will you be my maid of honor?
Holy shit. Do you mean it? - Yes.
Yes I will.
I love you. You too.
Come here. - Now I have two brothers.
There is more to your rotten be yourself-fest than your sell-out party. Fat.
It's actually good for you, we are ready -
- To help you with your forhudelsesperiode because you helped us.
We have served røvmange money. Eight bucket full.
And we can not accommodate all the new ones. - Now we can afford to fill two houses.
Can we rent your house for the additional members?
It's just a thought.
We are ready to give you four cans a month in rent.
Five.
Five. We go with the five. - Five cans per month.
So we say five buckets. - How!
We have won! Can you supply each month? - Yes. When can we move in?
Now. I fucking care. - Landlords. How hard can it be?
We make it damn. - Fucking!
Yes! Ekstrafest!
RENTED
Male...
I'm going to miss the house.
Our first house. - How Stella was a baby.
There she took the first step.
There she said her first words.
And we measured her.
Can you see the lines? Do you remember them?
It goes fast, right? - Yes, it's crazy. Okay.
Come on.
Are you coming?
This is our new house. - You can not even see the neighbors.
I think that we are good parents. We have been parents for Teddy.
We have been parents for 30 crazy girls.
We do our best. And more could you not ask, do you?
But whether we are good parents or not -
- And our daughters one day look at us like they fraternity girls.
They do not want anything to do with us. - It's just going to cry about.
Mor?
Are you afraid? - I'm afraid.
Come here, sweetie.
Hey, hottie. - Here, sweetie.
Would you like to sleep? - Not yet.
Not yet? Do you just enjoy a little first?
Shall we peek physician-boh? Peep-boh!
Peep-boh! - Peep-boh!
Peek-a-boo. You we will always be sweet to us, right?
We will always be best friends and have something to talk about, right?
Hey sweety. - Hey sweety.
I'm sorry not of it. - No.
I love you, baby. - So do I.
3 MONTHS LATER
How are you? Well? - Yes. I've got some nerves.
You look amazing. - Thank you.
It goes? You seem very nervous. - I'm a little upset.
You should just remember -
- Darren is the one who loves you maximum worldwide.
Darren appreciate your friendship.
Darren can not imagine a life without you.
And Darren is proud to call you his best friend.
You're not talking about Darren, do you? - No.
Let's get you married.
Okay, wake up, folks.
Gom 1 and his best man is ready. Are you ready for us?
I am proud of you. You found your niche. - Yes, gay wedding planner.
It's a great job, and you may well be punished.
My only competence is party planning, and gays like me.
It's because you're a great guy. - Thank you.
And they might want to fuck you. - You said it, not me.
Delta Psi.
- Delta Psi.
Now you need to get married. - Yes.
We are on the way.
So we are at home with baby Mildred!
How are you? - How was the birth?
It's over. - Yes.
Spoon on the table? - No.
I did not. - Prof.
Do you have a gift for your new baby sister? - The child's first dildo.
Thank you, Stella. - It's like us.
Show it to them. - It's Jimmy juniors favorite.
Our vibrators should not have veins. Maybe I obtain one without buns.
Get it away.
Want to meet your cousin, Jimmy junior?
See her once. Try to see. The families meet.
Se dem.
- Hold da op.
Hey, Jimmy junior. My name is Mildred. - Where sweet.
Hello. One day we two will fuck.
No never.
Mother and father will teach me about self-respect, so I stick by your type.
I could go on all day. Now we go.
Thank you fit Stella. It was really cool.
She is beautiful. - Hi.
We did it. We've got a child. - We've got another one.
I love you. - I love you too.
Do you kiss your sister, Stella?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org